Built on dead and broken trees, fast food, freedom, battery scenes.
Amber waves of gasoline, turf decays on every screen.
They sleep strapped in tit-fall hats, scream fake news in maggot chats.
History whitewashed on top of the wall, the empire promoted and bound to fall.
We're living in a state of delusion, as in denial, a toxic religion.
Stars and lights on every flint, the old side, but most said, yeah, we're a fat-bound institution.
We're dying brown in a state of delusion.
Billionaires fly while bridges collapse, we chase the dream with broken maps.
Pelt chairs are awful, schools are broke, but we still laugh at porn.
Full of tricks and nonsense, lost and rare, what might all be if?
So many noise there, but we're all twirls, sippin' Red Bull and Vodka Snooze.
We're living in a Sandalusian world through faith and ambition.
Truth is meant on passive text, justice goes to reason act.
The act went from legion to confusion, we're bleeding out in a Sandalusian.
This is finally all set, what's on the toilet bucket?
We're all blazers on cable rails.
We can't seem to draw civil wars at all with this.
Still living in a state of delusion, manifest destiny, mass seclusion.
Your fear sees all the new constitution, and we're too damn proud for a revolution.
Scream out this grand illusion.
We're the bus line in a state of delusion.